I Believe I Can Fly
我相信我能飞翔
歌手：R. Kelly(Robert Sylvester Kelly)
压制:随Feng
I used to think that I could not go on
我原以为我无法坚持下去
And life was nothing but an awful song
生命只不过是首忧郁的歌
But now I know the meaning of true love
但现在我明白了真爱的含义
I'm leaning on the everlasting arms
找到了可以永久依靠的臂膀
If I can see it, then I can do it
只要我能看见希望 我就能成功
If I just believe it, there's nothing to it
如果我相信我能行 那就没有什么不可以
I believe I can fly
我相信我能飞翔
I believe I can touch the sky
我相信我能触到天空
I think about it every night and day
日日夜夜 我想象这一幕
Spread my wings and fly away
展翅高飞......
I believe I can soar
我相信我能高飞
I see me running through that open door
我看见我穿过那敞开的生命之门
I believe I can fly
我相信我能飞翔
See I was on the verge of breaking down
看 我在崩溃堕落的边缘
Sometimes silence, it can seem so loud
有时沉默也能震耳欲聋
There are miracles in life I must achieve
生命中很多奇迹等我去实现
But first I know it starts inside of me
但我知道要实现奇迹 就必须先从我做起
If I can see it
如果我还能看见希望
Then I can do it
我就能成为那个我想成为的人
If I just believe it
我相信我能行
There's nothing to it
那就没有什么不可以
I believe I can fly
我相信我能飞翔
I believe I can touch the sky
我相信我能触到天空
I think about it every night and day
日日夜夜 我想象这一幕
Spread my wings and fly away
展翅高飞......
I believe I can soar
我相信我能高飞
I see me running through that open door
我看见我穿过那敞开的生命之门
I believe I can fly
我相信我能飞翔
Hey, cause I believe in me, oh
因为我相信自己
If I can see it
如果我还能看见希望
Then I can do it
我就能成功
If I just believe it
我相信我能行
There's nothing to it
那就没有什么不可以
I believe I can fly
我相信我能飞翔
I believe I can touch the sky
我相信我能触到天空
I think about it every night and day
日日夜夜 我想象这一幕
Spread my wings and fly away
展翅高飞......
I believe I can soar
我相信我能高飞
I see me running through that open door
我看见我穿过那敞开的生命之门
I believe I can fly
我相信我能飞翔
Hey, if I just spread my wings
只要我张开自己的翅膀
I can fly
我可以飞翔
Hey, If I just spread my wings
只要我张开自己的翅膀
I can fly
我可以飞翔
压制:随Feng